Now I will introduce you to the update of the UI-related functions.
In the new version of 2025.1,
we have optimized and updated the library.
We have added the label page of Connect Shop,
which is more convenient to purchase and download assets on it,
and we have synchronized the selection function of the web page,
which allows you to find the content you need more quickly.
Go to the library and click Connect Shop.
First, let's find a free fabric asset double click.
You can see that the fabric is directly added to the object window.
Let's try to drag a free clothing asset directly.
You can see that there is also an additional asset search and selection function here.
We can choose clothing first and open the selector.
You can see that there are gender and age, style and other options corresponding here.
Then we can select one of the five asset options.
We can make a selection according to the assets we want.
You can also search and input the keyword to look for.
You can see this clothing is directly added.
The selection options corresponding to different asset types are also different.
Now let's try to buy a paid clothing asset, at this time we need to right-click on the asset,
we can see that the purchase car will appear and open in Connect, click on the purchase car and open the purchase car,
you can see that you can check the assets that have been added in the purchase car, click on the purchase will automatically jump to the purchase interface,
after the purchase is completed, the assets can be added to our project, we can also check the purchase record at the bottom,
your purchased assets will be recorded here and classified,
we can see that the 2025.1 design optimization can make it easier for us to add assets from Connect to the business city,
to find and use resources more quickly,
In the new 2025.1 version, the virtual model information display function has been added to the semi-transparent surface,
allowing users to check the relationship between the model and the version while editing the version,
at the same time, the display grid of the virtual model can be added to the bottom separately,
it can be more convenient to use, when we are making clothing, we hope to be able to see the relationship between the clothing and the virtual model in all directions,
for example, when the virtual model is the physical surface or the black and white surface, we cannot directly check the relationship between the dragon and the virtual model,
some of the dragon version will be blocked by the model, we go to the 3D vertical menu, find the virtual model information display, choose semi-transparent surface,
at this time, we can see that the virtual model is semi-transparent, you can check the clothing and the dragon,
and objectively see whether the sleeves are in harmony with the virtual model,
in the virtual model information display, open the display grid, when we use the display grid,
while switching the model information display, it can also maintain the grid display state,
and then we can see that the virtual model is in harmony with the model.
The cloud 2025.1 gives users the advantage of virtual model display,
so users can check the clothing and virtual model information more objectively,
and have a more comfortable experience during the creation process,
in the previous version,
When you import or export a 3D file, you can select the desired option below and save it in the Preview File Manager, and you can also name the preview.
Next time you import or export a file, you only need to select the preset option you saved.
Click on the 3D file, select import, and use the FBX file as an example.
Find the FBX file, click open.
Change the settings below.
Click Add, you will see a preset path here.
You can set it yourself.
After setting the preset path,
you can name the preset name and import preset1.
Click OK.
Now we can delete this FBX file.
Let's try to import FBX again.
When you change the following settings, you will find that the preset has become the selected configuration.
At this point, click Add in the preset.
Create a new preset name and import preset2.
Now you can see that there are two preset options that you have previously set up.
Click to confirm the import.
Next time when you need to export FBX files with the same settings, you can select the settings you have previously created.
Then the export file is also the same, click to import the file.
Select the save location to change the export settings below.
Click to add preset path and name.
Next time when you export FBX files, you can select the same settings as before.
In the new version of Kolo, the new configuration is used to import and export files.
It can save time and provide direct path for users.
In the new version, the 2D quick photo function has also been updated.
In the 2D quick photo, a new 2D line option has been added.
You can change the color and type of the line here.
Find the file and open the 2D version of the quick photo.
The 1-to-1.
By pressing the button left, 2D 1-to-1, the 2D quick photo play window appears.
The 2D fast photo slide window appears.
You can see the screen compare to the previous version.
This version can more directly view the line option and other information options.
You can change the lines in the line option to point curve lines and holo lines,
and you can also change the color of the line.
Here we can see that the base line and the cutout are displayed separately.
When you have set up the option of 2D quick photo, you can choose to save it.
At the same time, the quick photo function in the cherry blossom release mode has also been updated.
The 2D quick photo optimization update allows users to more freely edit the output effect of the 2D version and have more self-determined choices.
When users adjust the clothing version in the building, it is necessary to ensure that the unit is the same size as the actual clothing.
In the new version 2025.1, you can adjust the number of small numbers in the system.
Select a line to view.
Currently, only one small number can be seen.
Open the settings.
Navigate to the user self-definition.
User interface.
Find the unit small number.
The small number can be set to 1-5 by itself, allowing us to change the number of small numbers to 4.
Click for adjustment.
Jump to the user profile.
Go to the driver'sуйnc.com box.
The information we are going to stained up here indicates that there's no issue with the cameo issues in the original photos.